sup everyone T 5 here with a very
special video today and you're probably
wondering why I'm here cosplaying as
manic like with this [__] wristband
[__] well that's there's a simple answer
to that [__] I'm [__] pissed why
am I pissed cuz I just released a so on
christas special and people didn't
really get it like I released the video
and by the end it they thought like
Bobby was the bad guy the [__] bad
guy can you believe this I can't the
reason they thought he was a bad is
because at the end of the [__] movie
and [__] Bob I gave everyone [__]
trees as if he as if that's a [__]
bad thing and I guess the reason people
got mad is because they said oh Bobby is
being mean because he gave everyone the
shitty trees and that's not it [__]
like Bobby gave every the trees they
were looking at in the [__] like um
in the PO section and [__] so Bobby
didn't do anything wrong and I'm kind of
pissed cuz a lot of people said oh
that's what here's what pissed me the
[__] if if you didn't pick up what I'm
saying [__] like people are saying
Bobby was the bad guy of the christas
special he was not the bad guy the it
was the [__] the poor people the cop
The Peasants that did not appreciate
Bobby they did didn't appreciate what
what he gave him you know what I mean
[__] and when Bobby gave them the
[__] trees they were like what the
[__] is this but Bobby just gave them
the trees that they were looking at like
what what was Bobby going to do
give them different Christmas trees
Bobby owned that [__] farm he has all
the records of the trees that people are
looking at he saw the Hedgehogs were
looking at the shitty ass trees why was
were they look at shitts trees because
Bobby told his [__] to take his family
to look at the [__] trees you get
what I mean like Bobby didn't do
anything wrong Bobby did everything
right this is one of those [__]
stories and [__] that some people didn't
get because I guess I'm I'm too small
for them and [__] like MyQ was like like
damn [__] it's like higher than
everyone [__] else's on Earth was I'm
not [__] surprised cuz the locks are
around
[__] oh if you wonder why I have this
like L this L keychain instead of this
one it's cuz I like this one better like
this one this one looks cool although
this one looks better because it looks
funny and that that's why I got
it although going back to what I was
saying I am Fe oh [__] did I say why I
was holding this one oh oh damn I forgot
I forgot I didn't say why I'm cosing as
mic the reason I'm cosing as mic [__]
is because like there is no other
character not going no other media that
can tell [__] off a good old am the
Hedgehog am I right like I am right
that's why I know I'm right you're wrong
[__] you think so you goodbye I don't
nobody nobody nobody needs your ass and
I'm wearing this hos costume to channel
the the power to to [__] talk people and
[__] and that's why so if you have any
problems with like the the christas
special well you're just
wrong